inpwrd.com 2017-06-06

# inPowered Privacy Policy | inpwrd.com

Our privacy policy explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by inPowered, Inc. ("inPowered" or "we") with respect to your access to and use of inPowered services, whether through our website (located at http://amplify.inpwrd.com) or in connection with the inPowered online social amplification tool (referred to below as the "inPowered Services").

Information We Collect

We collect certain information you provide to us when using the inPowered Services, such as when you we create an account for you or when you send us an email. We collect certain personal information that can be used to identify you, like your user name, email address, together with your company, and business postal address, as well as certain non-identifying information, like your zip code.

We also automatically collect certain information when you use the inPowered Services, such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, operating system, browser type, the address of a referring site, and your activity with the inPowered Services, including access times and dates and other statistics. This information is not treated as personal information unless we combine it with or link it to any of the personally identifiable information mentioned above.

We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies" or web beacons. These are small files that your browser places on your computer. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our services, and to improve our services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

How We Use the Information We Collect

We use the information collected through the inPowered Services for the purposes described below: 

  * to provide the inPowered Services or information you request, and to process and complete any transactions;
  * to respond to your emails, submissions, questions, comments, requests, and complaints and provide customer service;
  * to monitor and analyze usage and trends, and to personalize and improve the inPowered Services and your experiences when you use the inPowered Services, such as providing content or features that match your interests, and to increase the functionality and user friendliness of our inPowered Services;
  * to send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, our inPowered Services; and
  * for any other purpose for which the information was collected.

Information We Share With Third Parties

  * We will not share the personal information we have collected from you, except as described below:
  * with service providers who are working with us in connection with the operation of the inPowered site or inPowered Services (these service providers have access to your personal information only to perform services on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose it or use it for any other purposes);
  * we may share aggregated information and non-identifiable information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, and other similar purposes;
  * when you give us your consent to do so, including if we notify you that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information;
  * when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants, or court orders;
  * to enforce or apply our privacy policy, our terms of use, or our other policies or agreements; and
  * in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition, or in any other situation where personal information may be disclosed or transferred as one of our business assets.

We are not responsible for the actions of service providers or other third parties, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to any third parties.

Links to Other Sites

The inPowered site or inPowered Services may contain links to other sites. Any information you provide on those sites is provided directly to the owner of that site and is subject to that party's privacy policy. Our privacy policy does not apply to such sites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of those sites.

Steps We Take To Protect Your Information Online

We take reasonable measures to protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.

Accessing and Modifying Your Information

If you have an inPowered account, you can access and modify the personal information you provided us that is associated with your account. You may cancel your account and delete your information at any time by sending an email to support@inpwrd.com. We will take steps to delete your information as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records and as otherwise required by law.

International Users

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, we may transfer your information to the United States and process it there (or any other country where we operate). By using the inPowered Services, you consent to the collection, transfer, use, storage, and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy policy.

Our Policy Toward Children

Our service is not directed to people under the age of 18 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from people under 18 years of age. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible.

Changes

Any information that is collected is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise our privacy policy from time-to-time. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on the inPowered site or by sending you an email or other notification, and we will indicate when such changes will become effective. By continuing to access or use the inPowered Services after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised policy.

Contacting Us

In you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@inpwrd.com.

Effective: August 13, 2012
